user authentication there are two main ways to get the job done
用户身份验证完成工作的主要方法有两种
sessions and tokens the traditional approach on the web is cookie-based
会话和令牌网络上的传统方法是基于 cookie 的
server-side sessions the process begins with a user filling out their username
服务器端会话 该过程始于用户填写其用户名
and password and then submitting it to a server which then validates it creates a
和密码，然后将其提交到服务器，然后 验证它
session in the database then responds with a session id the
在数据库中创建一个会话，然后用一个会话 ID 响应
session id will be saved in the browser's cookie jar
会话 ID 将保存在浏览器的 cookie jar 中
which is a place in the browser to save key value pairs that will be sent back
，这是浏览器中保存键值对的地方，该键值对将
to the server on each subsequent request it can then respond back with content
在每次后续请求时发送回服务器然后可以用
designed for the currently logged end user
为当前登录的最终用户设计的内容进行响应
in other words we have a stateful session between the front end client
，换句话说，我们在前端客户端
and backend server this approach works great but there are some drawbacks it
和后端服务器之间有一个有状态的会话，这种方法效果很好，但是有一些缺点，它
can be vulnerable to an attack known as cross-site request forgery where the
可能容易受到称为跨站点的攻击 请求伪造
attacker points the user to a site they're logged into to perform
攻击者将用户指向他们登录的站点以
actions they didn't intend to like submitting a payment or changing their
执行他们不打算喜欢的操作提交付款或更改 ir
password although the risk is very low especially
密码虽然风险非常低，特别是
if you use a modern framework to implement your code the bigger problem
如果您使用现代框架来实现代码，更大的问题
is that you'll need to store the session id
是您需要将会话 ID 存储
in a database or keep it in memory on the server because most of today's
在数据库中或将其保存在服务器的内存中，因为当今的大多数
cloud applications are scaled horizontally this can be a huge
云应用程序 水平扩展，这可能
bottleneck in production and that brings us to token-based
是生产中的一个巨大瓶颈，这将我们带到基于令牌的
authentication which solves this problem but introduces its own set of challenges
身份验证，它解决了这个问题，但引入了自己的一组挑战，
the process begins the same with the client sending its login details to the
该过程开始于客户端将其登录详细信息发送到
server instead of storing a session id it generates a json web token the jot is
服务器而不是存储 会话 id它生成一个 json Web 令牌
created with a private key on the server then it's sent back to the browser where
使用服务器上的私钥创建 jot然后将其发送回浏览器，在将来的请求中
it's normally kept in local storage on future requests the jot will be added
它通常保存在本地存储中 jot 将添加
to the authorization header prefixed by bearer the server then only
到以承载服务器为前缀的授权标头中 那么只
needs to validate the signature there's no need for a database lookup somewhere
需要验证签名就不需要
else in the infrastructure and that's way more efficient when
在基础设施中的其他地方进行数据库查找，这样效率更高
dealing with a distributed system in the cloud
处理云中的分布式系统，
however tokens can still be hijacked by an attacker and they can also be
但是令牌仍然可能被攻击者劫持，并且它们也可能
difficult to invalidate and they can't be used to authenticate a
难以失效，并且它们不能用于
user in the background on the server here's the most important thing to
在服务器的后台对用户进行身份验证这是最重要的要
understand with a session the authentication state is handled on the
理解的事情 一个会话身份验证状态在服务器上处理，
server while tokens are managed on the client
而令牌在客户端上管理
this has been user authentication in 100 seconds
这已经是 100 秒内的用户身份验证
if you want to master web security check out web security academy
如果你想掌握网络安全，请查看网络安全学院
my friend bartos is launching a 12-week coaching program
我的朋友 bartos 正在启动一个为期 12 周的辅导计划
it's not your ordinary course but 12 weeks of high-value group-based learning
它不是 您的普通课程，但 12周的高价值基于小组的学习
and i'm teaching my own module in the course on firebase security check out
，我在 Firebase 安全课程中教授我自己的模块查看
the link in the description to learn more and i will see you there in a few
描述中的链接以了解更多信息，我将在几周后见到您，
weeks thanks for watching
谢谢 观看